Guide to the Jascha Heifetz Collection ARS.0046
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Reel Tapes, 1954-12-14 to 1972-11-21
  - Box 26, 1953 -- 1961; 17 10 1/2" open reel tapes
    - Miscellaneous Tape, 195-; 1 10 1/2" open reel tape (Box 26, Reel 17)
      [Jascha] Heifetz: Mendelssohn VC [violin concerto, Guido] Cantelli, NYPSO [New York Philharmonic Symphony Orchestra] 1954
      use 2nd take - first one NG
      Information handwritten in black ink on sheet of paper inside box:
      Track 1 Egon Petri recital at S.F. Conservatory 11/29/59 All Busoni
      15 min 1. Indian Diary; All Italia ! Perpetuum Mobile
      30 min 2. Sonata in e op. 36A w/Hans Basserman, violin
      25 min 3. Fantasia Contrappuntistica w/Carlo Bussotti, piano